Excuse me, sir. Sir, is this your Bugatti?
It is.
And what did you do to
be able to afford a Bugatti?
One second, man.
One second. We have one of the
biggest media channels in the entire world.
We grew a channel to 10 million followers.
Could we get one quick minute with you?
I think you interviewed one of my friends.
What's that? What's that?
We interviewed one of your friends?
Yes. I'm an entrepreneur.
What was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
My last case was the
Deepwater Horizon that generated $28 million.
Oh, I did this. Well, I
did 80 million in one day.
You did 80 million in one day?
80 million in one day, and we
may break that this year on Saturday.
Are you serious?
Yeah, I'm serious.
What's your main business?
Well, it depends on which day it is,
but commercial real estate is what I focus in.
But then I do a hell
of a lot of other things.
What was the most amount of
money you made in a year?
The most money I made was
$15 million after taxes and everything else.
So did you have to pay
a lot of money in taxes?
Zero dollars in taxes.
This is legal.
It's not just legal. It's written in the IRS code.
They're encouraging you to do it.
You came out of a Bugatti.
This is a lot of people's dream car.
How can somebody own a Bugatti in today's world?
You guys, I'm back in one of
the wealthiest cities in the entire world.
We're in Scottsdale, Arizona, home
to some of the wealthiest Americans,
from multimillionaires to billionaires.
And I'm going to be going around to
find and ask some of the wealthiest people
in this city how they created their
wealth, the playbook, the blueprint that it took,
and how you can do the
exact same thing and become financially free,
no matter what industry you're in in 2025.
So with that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir. Sir. Sir.
Question for you.
Have you ever been broke before?
Fuck no.
I've had a broken heart.
Have you ever had a broken heart?
No, sir.
Let me ask you this.
What line of business did you end up in?
I'm in all kinds of businesses.
So I have one of the biggest
business media channels in the world called
The School of Hard Knocks.
I go all over the country.
I'm based in Austin asking business owners
a couple of questions.
Give me two questions.
I'll answer them.
What's your main business?
Well, it depends on which day it is.
But commercial real estate is what I focus on.
But then I do a hell
of a lot of other things.
People say you have to have
a lot of capital to get started.
You have to.
No, you got to have a fucking brain
and you need to work your ass off.
And when everything falls apart, guess what?
Get your bootstraps on. Fucking go attack.
Yeah.
Let me ask you this.
Real quick, in terms of revenue, what was the
most amount of money you made in a year?
My best year was, fuck, $3.75 million.
That's for yourself?
Fact.
How about for the business?
I mean, fuck the business.
That's for myself.
Yeah.
I sell real estate.
But as a multi-year.
So I don't have, I mean,
that's what I made in one year.
Why was real estate your
vehicle out of all the businesses?
Shit house luck.
I graduated from the University
of Arizona with my finance degree,
and I was planning on going into selling stocks, right?
Being a financial planner these days.
Silly names.
From there, I had an opportunity
to interview with Grub & Ellis,
which is no longer now, it's Newmark.
And I got into commercial real estate.
And they said, hey,
the only thing open is land.
Fortunately, we have a ranch and a farm
back in western Kansas that I worked on.
And so I knew how to sell land
just because I knew farmers and I understood farmers.
And then the rest kind of became history.
Create friendships with your clients.
That's the other thing.
You only need two to three clients.
Focus on them, become good friends with
them, and then be there for them.
Be brothers.
So you like that repeat business
with just a couple of people.
Redundancy is very important.
You don't need a thousand different
people that you have to serve.
It depends on what industry you're in.
In my industry, you don't.
You need two to three clients.
And you ended up making more than one.
More than 99.9% of business professors ever will.
What's the lesson about business you'd
give to somebody that they will not?
Well, remember, professors are too
scared to enter the real world.
That's why they keep professing, right?
Haha.
They're pros at nothing.
Yeah.
You know, except, oh, here's what we can do.
They don't they don't know how the real world works.
Give me a lesson about business.
You give it somebody they
will not be taught in school.
Have they ever told you never quit?
I told you that's the third time I said it.
That's redundant, right? Never quit.
That is what separates a winner from a loser.
You got amazing advice, my friend.
Yeah.
So much for you.
God bless you.
And if you lost everything tomorrow,
could you make it all back?
Fuck yeah.
I'll be no longer twice on Sunday.
Haha. Wow.
That's called confidence.
Wait, wait, wait.
Say that again.
That's called confidence.
How did you find the
self-belief to make millions of dollars?
How did I what?
How did you find the self-belief
to go make millions of dollars?
Because people doubt themselves.
I started to see my results.
Yeah.
And realized that I was just not going to fail.
And so I just kept working.
You believe in God?
Oh, cool.
Yes, I believe in God.
Faith has been pretty important for you?
Faith.
Faith was not important for me starting out.
Yeah.
But faith is unbelievably important.
I love it.
Give it all to God.
By the way, you want
to know the secret of success?
Give it all to God.
Thank you, my friend.
It's all God's plan, brother.
I love it.
Have a great day, brother.
Thank you so much.
That was an incredible interview, and we're headed
right now to go get our next interview.
But I want to give you guys some game.
One thing I've noticed after interviewing and
spending a ton of time with ultra
successful entrepreneurs is how
seriously they take their privacy,
especially when it comes to their communication.
In today's world, you have to protect
your data now more than ever before.
And that's why
I use ProtonMail.
Unlike big tech email providers, ProtonMail
doesn't monetize or harvest your data.
Your emails stay private, ad
free and fully encrypted, meaning
even if their servers were ever compromised, no
one, not even Proton, can access your messages.
And if you think changing email providers is a
lot of work, why don't you just try it first?
You can easily keep your Gmail for your
junk emails and use ProtonMail for the important stuff.
So if you care about privacy and want an
email provider that actually cares about you and your data,
check out ProtonMail.
Using my link in the
description and then the pinned comment.
But with that being said,
let's go get this next interview.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, is this your Bugatti?
It is.
And what did you do to
be able to afford a Bugatti?
Yeah, I got it.
One second.
We have one of the biggest
media channels in the entire world.
We grew to 10 million followers.
Could we get one quick minute with you?
One of my friends.
What's that?
You interviewed one of my friends.
We interviewed one of your friends.
Yes.
I'm an entrepreneur.
You're an entrepreneur.
I am.
How many businesses do you own?
I've owned several over the past few decades.
Yeah.
Do you think we could interview
you for one minute real quick?
Sure.
What business has made you the most money?
The car business.
You're in the car business.
I am in the car business.
Throughout your career, what was the most amount
of money that you made in a single year?
Well, I did 80 million in one day.
You did 80 million in one day?
80 million in one day and we
may break that this year on Saturday.
Are you serious?
Yeah, I'm serious.
Were you a good student in school?
I was a horrible student in school.
I had ADD.
They didn't know what it was back then.
But it's actually been a
blessing because it gives me creativity.
It gives me vision.
It gives me energy.
I put really focused A-types with B-type personalities
around me so they're calm, focused, and driven.
What's a lesson about business you'd give to
somebody that they will not be taught in school?
The world will teach you if you listen.
The difference between Elon Musk launching rockets all the
time that blow up and he learns from everyone
or Boeing waiting five years to put
up one perfect that then doesn't work.
The difference is don't be afraid to take a chance.
If you don't swing, you'll never hit a home run.
That's game right there.
That's the game.
Thank you.
A couple more for you.
Sure.
I know you interviewed my friend
and I stepped away at that time.
I saw you.
That's why I recognized you when you walked up.
But entrepreneurs share a passion
of they love what they do.
Otherwise, you don't work this hard.
What's your best sales advice
to anybody in business right now?
Always tell the truth.
Under-promise and over-deliver and
you'll have customers for life.
So how important is it
to keep your word in business?
It's the most important.
My dad was known and I believe I'm the
same way even though we have attorneys and contracts.
If I shake your hand, it's a done deal.
And that's the way I was raised.
Honesty, integrity and transparency are the three
words that we run this company by.
And I believe that should be in any
industry that people should believe what you're telling them.
We do the best job,
I believe, of vetting the cars.
Not every car is perfect, but we
describe it as what it actually is.
I've sold cars to people around the world.
I've gone to their collections.
And I was in Dubai recently and a
very high-profile car guy, I went to his house.
He showed me the cars.
He goes, I have a compliment for you.
I bought that car from you.
Your cars always come in
better than the descriptions, not worse.
He goes, so I feel
confident buying sight unseen from you.
What is the best life advice you could
give to any 20-year-old watching this right now?
The biggest decision you make in your
life is the wife that you marry.
If they don't love what you
do, then you're going to have friction.
If they join along with you and they love what
you do, every day is much more of a pleasure
because you are both focused on the same thing.
You're focused on the same goal.
You've got to find somebody who becomes
part of the solution, not the problem.
Absolutely.
Now, what time are you coming home?
It's almost the opposite.
My wife loves what we do and I have
to drag her out of the office sometimes because she
shares the same passion and loves our customers
and my customers all have fallen in love with
her.
How old are you now?
I am 65.
65 years old.
I'm 22.
You've got about 40 years on me.
I do.
Whose generation works harder, yours or mine?
We'll see.
After this last election, I
am a whole lot more optimistic.
I think your generation is
cut to go do great things.
You've got amazing advice.
Thank you so much for your time.
Thank you.
I appreciate you.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
Yes, sir.
What did you do to become wealthy?
What do I do to become wealthy?
Well, it's interesting.
I will sit down and with all
my heart, I don't think about a box.
I don't think about working and building.
I think out of the box.
I build triangles.
So 1970, I'm sleeping in my car and I
said, God, there's got to be a better way.
There's got to be a better way.
And I went to work at McDonald's.
And there were 12 people.
And I said, this is ridiculous.
I extended the spatulas.
I extended where I put the buns in.
And I went down the tube.
And so from that point forward
is that I just make things better.
And my last case was the
Deepwater Horizon that generated $28 million.
Oh, my goodness.
So what line of business are you in?
Right now, it's a court reporting firm
that I have a lot of patents.
But right now, I play golf on tour.
Wow.
Yeah, I'm one of those guys.
Never been married.
Don't have children.
I was in an Indy car back in the day
and then trained with a retired SEAL team to lose over
100 pounds.
I'm one of those guys.
That's incredible.
So when you said a court
reporting room, were you like a lawyer?
Or what does that mean?
Yes.
You were a lawyer.
So that's what happens with that.
And then you just kind of stay in the moment.
You don't look at, you know,
we look at this guy's golf cart.
What can we do?
That looks kind of wobbly to me a little bit.
So what can we do to make that?
I just kind of think about what's a better way?
What can we do to make life better?
Not worry about what gender we are.
And I'm sure that's going to
piss off a lot of people.
But what we can do to make things a
better world, you know, for you, for him, for, you
know, can I get him a little strap that
he doesn't have to hold his hand so tight that
there's a shoulder strap that comes
down to where we can do that?
I just think like that.
Right.
How about your best negotiation advice?
A lot of people struggle to
close deals close to $28 million.
100% honesty, period.
Honesty.
When you're Italian, that's what you have.
There's two things you don't break.
And I think you know what they are.
What are they?
What are the two?
So folks, I'm sorry.
Your balls and your word.
You never break.
You never break either one of them.
So if I'm not looking for a problem, but
if there's a problem that arises, then I'm going
to finish it like a husband
or a boyfriend that beats his girlfriend.
It's going to be the last thing that
he does for a while type of thing.
So I'm just a guy that I say
what I mean and I mean what I say.
It's just that simple.
But you didn't come from money.
I did not.
How did you escape the cycle of poverty?
You just kind of look up
and say, God, show me the way.
I mean, I know that's not a popular word anymore.
And it's sad.
There was no drugs.
I've never done a drug in my life.
I don't drink because I suck at it.
So what's the best thing that I can do is
that I just think there's got to be a better
way.
And then I slowly from McDonald's
to coming forward to my own company.
There's so many opportunities for both of you.
What can you provide that other people don't?
Look at the vendors that
bring a cigar store in here.
Look at Barrett Jackson.
They'll do some ridiculous number this
year just by having cars come in.
Nobody thought about that before.
Think out of the box.
I've got amazing advice.
Thank you, sir.
I appreciate you, man.
My guy made $28 million in a single year
on the Deepwater Horizon case and just gave us
an incredible interview out here.
We got to go keep it rolling.
Go to another one out here.
Come on, you guys.
All right, you guys.
So since we're out in Arizona where some
of the wealthiest people in the world live, it's
only right that we run it with Pace
Morby, who's one of the most renowned real estate
entrepreneurs in the entire world.
A nine figure entrepreneur.
So we're about to go link up with Pace and
get some gain from him on how you can start
creating wealth in real estate without any money whatsoever.
Let's go link up with Pace.
And go see what he has to say.
Come on.
Who am I here with today?
Pace Morby.
And for those that don't know, what industry
did you decide to pursue a career in?
I started in construction and I ended up
getting in a way better industry, real estate and
lending.
And why was real estate your vehicle?
Out of all the businesses, the industries you
could have been in, why did you end up
in real estate?
I found that real estate was
the only guaranteed way to be successful.
There's a lot of ways to gamble with money.
Real estate's not gambling.
It's guaranteed.
Scientifically proven.
Numbers have shown for hundreds of years,
real estate is the most guaranteed investment
you could make.
How long have you been in real estate for?
I've been in real estate for 12 years.
I was a contractor touching real
estate for 10 years prior to that.
So let me ask you this.
Throughout your career, what was the most amount
of money that you've made in a single
year?
Most money I made was $15
million after taxes and everything else.
After taxes?
After taxes, yeah.
That's for yourself?
That's for myself, yeah.
My company that year, I think we
did like $115 million, something like that.
So did you have to pay
a lot of money in taxes?
$0 in taxes.
So because I'm a real estate investor,
we take advantage of the IRS code.
The IRS code allows me as a real
estate investor to pay $0 in federal income taxes.
Of course, I pay property taxes and
I have employees and I pay employment tax.
I pay all those kinds of taxes.
But federal income, I have not paid a
dollar in federal income tax in seven years.
How is that possible?
The way it's possible is the IRS rewards you
as a real estate investor and says, hey, if
you invest in real estate and you
provide affordable housing to the United States, we
will reward you with tax benefits that make
it so you pay $0 in federal income tax.
So is there a certain piece of real estate
or a piece of property that you should be
looking to buy in that case?
Any real estate works.
You can do any piece of real estate.
You can even do RV parks.
RV parks where it's primarily land that
you don't even have really any buildings on.
You could buy multifamily properties.
You could buy hotels.
You could buy single family.
It does not matter.
Any piece of real estate
will allow you to avoid taxes.
This is legal.
It's not just legal.
It's written in the IRS code.
They're encouraging you to do it.
The IRS wants you to do it
because they're wanting you to provide affordable housing
to the United States.
I mean, look what the United States does.
They don't know how to provide
affordable housing to our own country.
You look at LA right now.
They took state tax dollars and built a
big high rise for homeless people and they spent
$600,000 per one unit.
I could have done that thing for $75,000.
The government is not good at using our money
and so the IRS knows that and they reward
us to deploy our capital and provide affordable housing.
Now, your business did over $100
million in a single year consistently.
Let me ask you this.
How did you scale from eight to nine figures?
Secret to scaling is two things.
Number one, I can't do it on my own so
of course I need to delegate to high level people.
Pay people a lot of money,
you'll attract really high quality people.
If you pay peanuts, you'll get monkeys.
Remember that.
Good quality people.
Pay check.
That's number one.
Number two is get partners that
are the polar opposite of you.
My partner Josiah is the polar opposite of me.
I like to be on stage,
write books, do all the content.
I inspire people.
I attract employees to our team.
He goes out and manages those people, runs
the payroll, runs the books, makes sure everything's
taken care of so I can do my job.
Very similar to your guys' structure, you
have partners that are doing different things.
For me, give up a portion of your
ownership in your company to somebody who's the polar
opposite and brings different skills to the table.
I'd rather have a slice of
the pie than 100% of a grape.
All day.
I tell people that all the time.
I'd rather have one bite
of a watermelon than one grape.
As a nine-figure entrepreneur, what was the
best financial advice that you ever received?
Best advice I ever got was that most of
the advice you got all the way up until you're
probably 30 was a lie.
The reason why that person told you that
lie is because they were also lied to.
Specifically, what I was lied to about is
I need a bank to go buy real estate.
I need a loan to go buy real estate.
I need credit.
I need money.
Guys, I have half a billion dollars in
my portfolio and I've never used a bank.
I don't use credit.
I've literally never had my credit pulled.
I don't use any of my own money.
I just get creative finance.
I do everything creative finance.
That was the greatest piece of advice I got.
It was so good, I thought it was a scam.
I had to read five different books and
go ask 100 different people before I believed
that it was possible for me.
That was the greatest piece of advice
is that everything you thought about acquiring businesses,
vehicles, buildings for yourself, your own
house, real estate portfolios, literally no
bank, no credit, no cash, none
of that crap is needed at all.
How is that possible?
We go to sellers that are trying to retire typically.
We go to like an apartment
building, a seller's own for 30 years.
He wants to retire and he wants us
to give him a monthly check every single month.
And he says, I don't want
to deal with the property anymore.
And if he sold it on the market
for cash, he'd have a big capital gains tax.
And so when he sells it to us on seller
finance, he lets us make payments to him and he becomes
the bank.
Then I have no bank needed.
I have no credit needed and I
have no money out of my pocket either.
I can just start making payments to him.
Where do my payments come from?
From the tenants that are staying in the property.
One of our best ones is 160 units.
Brings in like $160,000 a month.
The seller, taxes, insurance, the
management, all the repairs, everything.
Our company brings in $53,000 a month on one property.
$53,000 a month net in our pocket with no
credit, no bank and no money out of our pocket.
Not even a dollar.
What's the deepest life quote you've ever heard?
One of my favorite quotes is a man convinced
against his will is of the same opinion still,
which means stop trying to convince the
world around you to believe in your vision.
They're just going to dig deeper that
they're not going to believe in your vision.
Go find the people that already believe
in you and double down on those relationships.
What I did for the longest time is I
tried to get my friends and my family to believe
in what I was doing.
And I wasted years.
So again, a man convinced against his will
is of the same opinion still, which means
if they don't believe in you today,
they're never going to believe in you.
Move on, go get a
different relationship and believe in yourself.
What was the lowest point in your life?
Lowest point of my life,
man, I've had some low ones.
I've had my brother's hung himself.
My brother that I shared
a room with my whole life.
My brother got, he got addicted to
fentanyl and my brother took his own life.
That was a low moment.
That same year, my wife and I got divorced.
I had a member of my family go to prison for
two years and I had to pay for the bills of
his family while he was in prison.
That was a low moment in my life.
I wrote a suicide letter to my family and
I was like, I'm going to drive a car into
a semi truck head on and
I was going to kill myself.
It was about your age, 23, 24 years old.
And my mom called me that day and checked in
on me and she said, Hey, I just, I don't
know why I should have checked on you today, but
I just want to let you know, I love you
and check in on you.
And I didn't kill myself.
And here we are 600 employees and
a hundred million dollars a year in revenue.
I'm grateful.
I didn't kill myself.
So in other words, you got to reach
out to those people that are around you checking
on them, make sure that they're doing good.
Yeah.
I mean, look in, look in your
phone and, and, um, reach out to people.
Everyone's not just new year's, not just
Christmas texts, people that are your friends
and just thank them for being
your friends and get around people.
Like what's cool is I was just in your
guys' group, you know, doing a zoom call with your
guys' community.
And it was really cool to see
how everybody's networking with each other and encouraging
each other and helping each other out with mindset.
Guys get up, get a part of these guys
as a community, go join their community, get involved
and get around people that
are doing more than you are.
And they'll inspire you.
And the number one thing I learned is
that people better than you will give you permission
to become better yourself.
Your parents, the people you go to
church with, they're not giving you permission.
To do that.
They're telling you to be humble.
They're telling you to be quiet.
They're telling you to be grateful for what you have.
Guys, I can be grateful for
what I have and still want more.
And the way to do that is get
into a community like you, what you guys have.
You got amazing advice, brother.
Thank you so much for your time.
I appreciate you, man.
That was excellent.
Yes.
You guys, Scottsdale was insane.
We interviewed some of the wealthiest people
and not just Scottsdale, not just Arizona,
but the entire country.
So I need you guys to
like, and subscribe for amazing content.
We have coming every single
week with the biggest business owners.
Some of the wealthiest people in the entire world.
And if you have not joined yet, if you
are not a member of my private entrepreneur community,
these school of mentors, you are missing out.
And the craziest thing is you can join
this community, which has become one of the biggest
and greatest communities for entrepreneurs in the
entire world for free inside of this
community.
Every single week I bring in the biggest
business owners, even billionaires on live calls to
directly mentor you, where you have the ability
to ask them a question about your career,
your life or your business.
So if you want to learn how to sell
like a millionaire or negotiate like one, or how
to start and scale that business, how to
find that winning product and market it, whatever
industry you're in, you can
come learn from millionaires and billionaires.
I interview on live calls inside of this community.
All you have to do is go down to the
link in the description of this video to join the
school of mentors today for free.
I can't wait to see you on the inside,
but with that being said, I'll see you in the
next video.